naijaflavour.com.ng 2019-04-18

# Privacy Policy | naijaflavour.com.ng

###### Privacy Policy

At [Naijaflavour.com.ng](https://www.naijaflavour.com.ng/), We take your privacy seriously.

This privacy policy pointedly describes what personal information we collect and how we use it on Naijacent.com Routine Information Collection. All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information pointedly includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this website. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes, and lets us know what pages and information are useful and helpful to visitors.

*** Cookies and Web Beacons**

Where necessary, this website uses cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.

Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.

*** Controlling Your Privacy**

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

*** Contact Information**

Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to an Administrator at Naijaflavour.com for further clarification.

  * A word filter has been put in place to prevent members from using sexually explicit words in their posts.

Let's hear your thought about this post. 

#### [CLICK HERE TO POST A COMMENT]

Attention!!! Our Music Promotion is Express » Clean » Classic » Dope » Well Packaged » And Very Cheap Whatsapp/Call >>> +2349061242061 Or email us @ admin@naijaflavour.com for sponsored adverts.
